<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Talha Ahmad</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Talha Ahmad</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 13:00:45 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nvim Config</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/nvim-config/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 13:00:45 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/nvim-config/</guid>
      <description>Neovim is my primary text editor of choice. In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll be breaking down my current configuration file and explaining the purpose of most plugins and settings. At the moment, I&amp;rsquo;ve tried to mantain a fairly simple configuration, but I&amp;rsquo;m always looking to improve it. I&amp;rsquo;ll try updating this article with any changes as time goes on. You can see my config here.&#xA;Structure I use lazy as my plugin manager, which I&amp;rsquo;ll get into, but my file structure at the moment looks like this:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wheelchair Phone Charger</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/wheelchair-phone-charger/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/wheelchair-phone-charger/</guid>
      <description>For my freshman year final engineering design project at McMaster University, I worked in a team of 4 individuals to design and create a design that would help a client assigned to us by the university. Our client was a young individual diagnosed with spina bifida, a condition that inhibits the development of the spinal cord and causes paralysis in the lower body. Our client used a wheelchair to move around and mentioned that they had difficulty charging their phone due to the location of charging ports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Essential Gist Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m a second year mechatronics engineering student at McMaster University. At the moment, I&amp;rsquo;m working as a software developer at Taylor Systems. I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about robotics, embedded systems, and software development. I&amp;rsquo;m always looking for new opportunities to learn and grow. To contact me, simply shoot me an email at talha05ahmad@gmail.com.&#xA;Areas of specialty The skills that I have actively developed and applied through projects and / or work experience include:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
